[mellow music]
[柔和的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [happy humming]
- [快乐的哼唱]
[fancy accordion music]
[美妙的手风琴音乐]
[French accent]
I am a culinary genius, no?
[法国口音]
我是一个烹饪天才，不是吗？
Here you are, sir.
在这里，先生。
Ze specialty of mah house.
麻屋的泽特产。
Roast salad à la Squidward.
鱿鱼烤沙拉。
[gasp]
Sacré bleu!
[喘气]
圣蓝！
I must apologize, monsieur!
我必须道歉，先生！
I have forgotten
the parsley for the garnish.
我忘记了
装饰用欧芹。
Stay warm,
my little Squidy.
保持温暖，
我的小乌贼
[smooch]
[亲吻]
[shrieks]
Le oww!
[尖叫声]
勒哇！
♪ ♪
Typical,
I always forget something.
典型的，
我总是忘记一些事情。
Ugh!
啊!
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[grunts angrily]
[愤怒地咕哝]
A sea bunny?
海兔？
- [laughter]
- [笑声]
- [shrieks sharply]
Ow!
- [尖锐尖叫]
噢！
[ukulele strumming]
[尤克里里弹奏]
[playful music]
[俏皮的音乐]
That voracious vermin is
ruining my French chef fantasy.
那只贪婪的害虫是
毁了我的法国厨师幻想。
Why--ah!
为什么——啊！
- [shrieks]
- [尖叫]
- Grr!
- 呃！
♪ ♪
Oh--oh, no, no, no, no.
哦——哦，不，不，不，不。
I have a ticklish core!
我有一颗怕痒的心！
[laughter]
[笑声]
Oh.
哦。
[sniffs]
[嗅嗅]
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
[fire alarms ringing]
[火警警报响起]
My roast à la Squidward!
我的烤鱿鱼！
[sizzling]
[嘶嘶声]
[sighs]
[叹气]
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- [sobbing]
- [抽泣]
- What the--
[growls]
- 什么是--
[咆哮]
Oof!
[gulps]
钱币！
[吞咽]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
["The Blue Danube"
by Johann Strauss II playing]
【《蓝色多瑙河》
由约翰·施特劳斯二世演奏]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic munching]
[有节奏的咀嚼]
♪ ♪
[record scratch]
[记录刮痕]
- I declare war on bunnies!
- 我向兔子宣战！
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- [blows raspberry]
- [吹覆盆子]
♪ ♪
- [jibbers]
- [叽叽喳喳]
♪ ♪
[groans exasperatedly]
[愤怒地呻吟]
[growls,
screams]
[咆哮，
尖叫声]
I am going to bury that bunny!
我要把那只兔子埋了！
[squeaks]
[吱吱声]
- [giggle,
burps]
- [咯咯笑，
打嗝]
[carefree humming]
[无忧无虑的哼唱]
- [gasp]
- [喘气]
Wow.
哇。
That's the ugliest eggplant
I've ever seen!
这是最丑的茄子
我见过！
I don't think
Squidward would mind
我不认为
章鱼哥会介意的
if I took a little taste.
如果我尝尝的话。
Ooh, come here.
哦，过来吧。
[both straining]
[双方都紧张]
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
[playful music]
[俏皮的音乐]
- [carefree humming]
- [无忧无虑的哼唱]
♪ ♪
[deep rumbling]
[低沉的隆隆声]
♪ ♪
[squeaks]
[吱吱声]
[sniffing]
[嗅嗅]
[gasp]
[喘气]
♪ ♪
- Ha, he's gonna fall
right into my trap.
- 哈，他会摔倒的
正好落入我的陷阱。
[laughs]
[笑]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
[shrieks]
[尖叫声]
[phone ringing]
- Hello, Animal Control?
[电话铃声]
- 你好，动物控制中心？
I've got a sea bunny
cornered in my garden
我有一只海兔
被困在我的花园里
and need assistance!
并需要帮助！
[tires screech]
[轮胎尖叫声]
♪ ♪
Did you have
to catch him that easily?
你有没有
这么容易就抓住他了？
- I demand the release
of this poor woodland creature.
- 我要求释放
这个可怜的林地生物。
He's got rights too,
you know.
他也有权利，
你知道。
- This is none of your
business, SpongeBob, go away.
- 这不属于你的
生意，海绵宝宝，走开。
- You want him?
You can keep him.
- 你想要他吗？
你可以留住他。
Saves me a trip
to the incinerator.
为我节省了一次旅行
到焚烧炉。
- Hooray!
- 万岁！
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
- I'm warning you, SpongeBob.
- 我警告你，海绵宝宝。
Keep that filthy animal
away from my--
保留那只肮脏的动物
远离我的——
- [sing-song voice]
Vegetables!
- [唱歌声音]
蔬菜！
That's what you like,
isn't it, bunny?
这就是你喜欢的，
不是吗，兔子？
We'll see what we got
in the fridge.
我们会看看我们得到了什么
在冰箱里。
- [sniffing]
- [嗅嗅]
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
- Whoops,
I'm out of veggies.
- 哎呀，
我没有蔬菜了
But I got something
even better.
但我得到了一些东西
甚至更好。
Gary's food! Yay!
加里的食物！耶！
[woman shrieks]
[女人尖叫]
Does bunny wunny
like his dinny winny?
兔子wunny吗
喜欢他的 dinny winny 吗？
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
All right, Gary's food is out.
Got it.
好吧，加里的食物吃完了。
知道了。
I'll get you veggies.
I'll be right back.
我给你买蔬菜。
我马上回来。
[wails]
[哀号]
[explosions]
[爆炸]
- [rumbling]
- [隆隆声]
[mischievous music]
[恶作剧的音乐]
♪ ♪
[shrieks]
[尖叫声]
[electricity fizzling]
[电嘶嘶作响]
- [sing-song voice]
Bunny wunny!
- [唱歌声音]
兔兔旺尼！
I've got a surprise
for you--
我有一个惊喜
为了你——
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[electricity crackling]
[电力噼啪声]
I'm gonna have to chew-proof
this whole house fast!
我得防咀嚼
这整个房子快！
Hot sauce ought
to do the trick.
辣酱应该
来做到这一点。
[playful music]
[俏皮的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [sniffing,
tongue smacking]
- [嗅，
咂舌]
[loud burp]
[大声打嗝]
[excited squeal]
[兴奋尖叫]
[naughty giggle]
[顽皮的傻笑]
[slurping noises]
[吸吮声]
[loud burp]
[大声打嗝]
♪ ♪
[slurping]
[发出声音]
[burp]
[打嗝]
[squeals]
[尖叫声]
- Huh? No, no, no, no!
- 啊？不，不，不，不！
[panicked squeaking]
[惊慌的尖叫声]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- [gulping,
sigh]
- [吞咽，
叹息]
- [panicked meow]
- [惊慌喵]
♪ ♪
- [loud burp]
- [大声打嗝]
- My comic books!
- 我的漫画书！
[battle cry]
[战斗呐喊]
- [gargling]
- [漱口]
[low whistle]
[低声哨声]
- I gotta get rid
of all that hot sauce.
- 我得摆脱
所有的辣酱。
[playful music]
[俏皮的音乐]
[slurping noises]
[吸吮声]
[tongue smacking]
[咂舌]
[shrieks sharply]
[尖锐尖叫]
Oh, oh, oh!
哦，哦，哦！
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
哦，哦，哦，哦！
[toilet whizzing]
[厕所的声音]
Here we are!
我们到了！
Water supply--check.
供水——检查。
Trampoline for hopping--check.
用于跳跃的蹦床——检查。
Buckteeth sharpener--check.
龅牙磨刀器——检查。
And an adding machine
for multiplying...
还有加法机
为了乘以...
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
Triple check-aroonie!
三重检查-阿鲁尼！
Now the bunny will be more than
happy to stay in his cage.
现在兔子将超过
很高兴呆在他的笼子里。
Huh?
啊？
- [sniffing]
- [嗅嗅]
[shrieks]
- [yelps]
[尖叫声]
- [尖叫声]
- [heavy breathing]
- [粗重的呼吸]
- Doesn't like cage...
- 不喜欢笼子...
Check.
查看。
- [heavy breathing]
- [粗重的呼吸]
[growls]
[咆哮]
[mischievous music]
[恶作剧的音乐]
- No, no, bunny,
don't go in there.
- 不，不，兔子，
不要进去。
You'll get lost!
你会迷路的！
I need my jellyfishing net.
我需要我的捕水母网。
Where did I put that thing?
我把那个东西放在哪里了？
Probably dropped
it in here somewhere.
可能掉落
它就在这里的某个地方。
Nyah, nyah--
ah, got it!
呀呀呀——
啊，明白了！
- Hello!
- 你好！
- Patrick, did you fall
between the cushions again?
- 帕特里克，你摔倒了吗
又在坐垫之间吗？
- No, SpongeBob,
I fell between the cushions.
- 不，海绵宝宝，
我跌倒在垫子之间。
But I have a solution
to your bunny problem.
但我有一个解决方案
解决你的兔子问题。
I love the hunt!
我喜欢狩猎！
♪ ♪
[crashes]
[崩溃]
[straining noises]
[紧张的声音]
- [panicked squeaking]
No, no!
- [惊慌的尖叫声]
不，不！
No, don't!
Please don't! That's my--
不，不要！
请不要！那是我的——
[crashes]
[崩溃]
All right, Patrick,
that's enough hunting.
好吧，帕特里克，
狩猎就够了。
You can come out now.
你现在可以出来了。
- I can't see where I'm going.
- 我看不到我要去哪里。
How do I get out of here?
我怎样才能离开这里？
[panicked screams]
[惊慌的尖叫声]
[distant]
SpongeBob, where are I?
[远方]
海绵宝宝，我在哪里？
- Stay where you are, Patrick!
I've got an idea.
- 留在原地，帕特里克！
我有一个主意。
To the pet shop!
去宠物店！
[video game jingle]
[panting]
[电子游戏顺口溜]
[气喘吁吁]
Thank you!
谢谢你！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
Patrick!
I bought a second bunny
帕特里克！
我又买了第二只兔子
to lure the first bunny
out of hiding.
引诱第一只兔子
从躲藏中出来。
- Hooray!
- 万岁！
[playful music]
[俏皮的音乐]
- [strains]
- [菌株]
♪ ♪
- [excited squeak]
- [兴奋的吱吱声]
♪ ♪
[sniffing]
[嗅嗅]
- [gasp]
- [喘气]
[tango music]
[探戈音乐]
♪ ♪
[accordion tango music]
[手风琴探戈音乐]
♪ ♪
- [straining]
- [紧张]
- Hold still, Patrick,
I see you.
- 保持不动，帕特里克，
我看到你了。
- [gasps, sighs]
Thanks, buddy.
- [喘气，叹气]
谢谢，伙计。
Aww, bunnies!
哇，兔子们！
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
[bunnies boinging]
[兔子的嗡嗡声]
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- One, two...
- 一，二……
Three?
三？
[bunnies giggling]
[兔子咯咯地笑]
- More bunnies!
- 更多兔子！
- [nervous laugh]
Yay!
- [紧张的笑声]
耶！
- [rumbling]
- [隆隆声]
[squeaking]
[吱吱声]
- Uh-oh.
- 呃哦。
Patrick, the hunt is on!
帕特里克，狩猎开始了！
[both ululate]
[两人都喊叫]
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
- Hey!
- 嘿！
Come back, bunny wunnies!
回来吧，小兔子们！
- [French accent]
This is the last carrot.
- [法国口音]
这是最后一根胡萝卜。
C'est la vie.
这就是生活。
- [excited hum]
- [兴奋的嗡嗡声]
- One more step,
and I will spit you on a roast!
- 再多一步，
我会把你吐在烤肉上！
I mean,
roast you on a spit!
我的意思是，
把你烤了！
[low rumbling]
[低沉的隆隆声]
Oh, oh, what's happening?
噢，噢，发生什么事了？
[rumbling]
[隆隆声]
- Don't worry, Squidward.
- 别担心，章鱼哥。
- Yeah.
We're here to help!
- 是的。
我们随时为您提供帮助！
- They're growing!
- 他们正在成长！
[shrieks]
[尖叫声]
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[panicked breathing]
[惊慌的呼吸]
[phone trilling]
[电话颤音]
Hello, Animal Control?
你好，动物控制中心吗？
Save me!
救救我吧！
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
[nervous blubbering]
[紧张的哭泣]
♪ ♪
[old man groan]
[老人呻吟]
[growls]
[咆哮]
[angry moaning]
[愤怒的呻吟声]
[spits]
[吐口水]
Get out of my house!
滚出我家！
Gah!
嘎！
That'll get them out.
这样就能把他们救出来了。
[wobbling noises,
crackling]
[颤抖的声音，
噼啪声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- Sorry about your house,
Squidward.
- 对不起你的房子，
章鱼哥。
- Yeah. We just heard.
- 是的。我们刚刚听说。
- [yelps]
- [尖叫声]
[chirping]
[叽叽喳喳]
[maniacal laughter]
[疯狂的笑声]
I'm a bunny now!
我现在是一只兔子了！
[crazy laughter]
I'm a bunny now!
[疯狂的笑声]
我现在是一只兔子了！
- Okay,
Mr. Tentacles, easy does it.
- 好吧，
触手先生，很容易做到。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [squeaks,
maniacal laughter]
- [吱吱声，
疯狂的笑声]
I'm a bunny now!
我现在是一只兔子了！
[laughter]
I'm a bunny now!
[笑声]
我现在是一只兔子了！
[bunnies purring]
[兔子咕咕叫]
- [angry Squidward noises]
- [章鱼哥愤怒的声音]
[toots clarinet]
[嘟嘟单簧管]
[mellow music]
[柔和的音乐]
♪ ♪